checkmystats.com.au 2007-12-02

# Checkmystats is an online provider of performance based marketing and sales solutions.

**Privacy   Statement**

The Checkmystats Team has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: [http://www.checkmystats.com.au](http://www.checkmystats.com/) 

Information gathered from your visit by our Web server is data of a general nature, the same that most Web servers would gather. Data such as IP address, pages served, average time of visit, and any errors encountered whilst visiting is collected in the server logs. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and the web page data helps us diagnose navigation problems, thus improving the layout and navigation of Checkmystats.

Checkmystats uses any information voluntarily given by our users to enhance their experience on our site, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements or to better prepare future content based on the interests of our users.

Also, Checkmystats uses information that users voluntarily provide in order to send out electronic newsletters.

### Further Details:

##### Link ID codes

ID codes are used in certain links to establish the relationship between you, checkmystats and the content and service providers. When these are used the data they contain only pertains to information required to establish this link so discounts and commissions (if applicable) can be paid to the relevant party.

##### Personal Information

Your e-mail address is not stored on the Internet when you subscribe to our Newsletter Services. When you subscribe to our newsletter services, your email address is used to send you those newsletter services only. Further, we do not give or sell the information collected by us to anyone for any use other than the purpose for which you gave it.

##### Newsletter Subscriptions (Ezines)

We send out newsletters to subscribers on a regular schedule (daily or weekly, depending on the newsletter), and occasionally send out special editions when we think subscribers might be particularly interested in something we are doing. Checkmystats never shares newsletter mailing lists with any uninvolved third parties, including advertisers or partners.

Checkmystats gathers the email addresses of users who voluntarily subscribe to newsletters at our site. Users may remove themselves from this mailing list by following the directions at the bottom of these publications.

##### Advertising

While aggregate counts of banner impressions and click through rates are provided to advertisers, an advertiser will never know that a specific user clicked their ad. Checkmystats does not target advertising against specific user information. Checkmystats will not provide specific user information to any third party company.

##### Usage tracking

Checkmystats tracks user traffic patterns. Checkmystats sometimes tracks and catalogues the search terms that users enter in [checkmystats.com.au](http://www.checkmystats.com.au/) search engine and directories, but the data tracked is never associated with individual users.

When we use tracking information to determine which areas of our sites users like and don't like based on traffic to those areas, we do not track what individual users read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This helps us continue to build a better service for you.

##### Cookies

A cookie is a small data file that can contain information such as a user ID that a site uses to track the pages you've visited. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Checkmystats uses cookies to track user traffic patterns, advertising banners displayed and when you click an advertising banner. Checkmystats advertising system stores one cookie to better track ad impressions and click rates.

If you've set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie.

You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use any Checkmystats site.

### Opt-out policy

Checkmystats gives users options wherever necessary and practical. Such choices include:

  * Opting not to sign up to receive our electronic newsletters

  * Opting out of allowing cookies to not be stored by turning them off in the browser (but please see above)

  * Opting not to participate in certain interactive areas, which completely alleviates the need to gather any personally identifiable information from our users

### Other Information

  * We do not use any special software used for detection purposes.

  * Adult sites, sites with adult-oriented links, sites that promote hatred, racism, or discrimination, and sites that promote illegal activity are banned from our service.

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact.

Kind Regards,

The Checkmystats Team
